ultrareach.com 2012-09-20

# Ultrareach - Privacy Policy

Protect your privacy online with  
anonymous surfing and browsing.  
Ultrasurf hides your IP address,  
clears browsing history, cookies,  
and more.

Using industry standard strong  
end-to-end encryption to  
protect your data transfer  
from being seen by third party.

Bypass internet censorship to  
browse the internet freely.

|     | 

This document was last updated on July 14, 2008.

  1. **ACKNOWLEDGEMENT AND ACCEPTANCE OF TERMS**

UltraReach Internet Corporation is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement sets forth our current privacy practices with regard to the information we collect when you or your computer interact with our website. By accessing UltraReach.Com, you acknowledge and fully understand UltraReach Internet Corporation's Privacy Statement and freely consent to the information collection and use practices described in this Website Privacy Statement.

  2. **PARTICIPATING MERCHANT POLICIES**

Related services and offerings with links from this website, including vendor sites, have their own privacy statements that can be viewed by clicking on the corresponding links within each respective website. Online merchants and others who participate in UltraReach Internet Corporation services are encouraged to participate in industry privacy initiatives and to take a responsible attitude towards consumer privacy. However, since we do not have direct control over the policies or practices of participating merchants and other third parties, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or contents of those sites. We recommend and encourage that you always review the privacy policies of merchants and other third parties before you provide any personal information or complete any transaction with such parties.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org. 

  3. **INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT**

UltraReach Internet Corporation collects certain information from and about its users directly from our Web Server logs. 

(1) **Web Server Logs.**   

When you visit our Website, we may track information to administer the site and analyze its usage. Examples of information we may track include: 

    * Your Internet protocol address (IP). 
    * Number of links you click within the site. 
    * Date and time of your visit. 
    * Web page you linked to our site from. 
    * Pages you viewed on the site. 

(2) **Personal Information Users**   

We will not disclose personally identifiable information we collect from our Web Server log to third parties except to the extent necessary including:

    * To fulfill your service requests for services. 
    * To protect ourselves from liability, 
    * To respond to legal process or comply with law, or
    * In connection with a merger, acquisition, or liquidation of the company.

  4. **CHANGES TO THIS STATEMENT**

UltraReach Internet Corporation has the discretion to occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the "updated" date at the top of this Privacy page. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates.

  5. **CONTACTING US**

If you have questions regarding our Privacy Statement, its implementation, failure to adhere to this Privacy Statement and/or our general practices, please contact us: [info9@ultrasurf.us](mailto:info9@ultrasurf.us)

UltraReach Internet Corporation will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly respond and resolve any problem or question.  
  
---|---|---
